Fiary Choerudin

Bandung ID

🛮 +628 1222 790 896 | 🔀 hi@fiqry.dev | 🖸 github.com/fiqryq | 🛅 linkedin.com/in/fiqrychoerudin

Personal Profile

I am a software developer from Bandung Indonesia currently working as Frontend engineer for 2 years. i am working on react environment and use Typescript as my primary programming language and also love Tailwind for my CSS Framework.

Education

Telkom University Bandung, ID

Diploma Informatic Enginering

Aug 2017 - Aug 2020

- · Head of Multimedia Labolatory Research
- · Graduate with GPA 3.38

Work Experience

Kitabisa Jakarta, Indonesia

Frontend Developer May 2022 - Present

· Working with campaigner squad to develop features related to the campaign.

- · Develop an internal product library called KBPL and already published some components like image, bottomsheet, chips, and menu navigation.
- · Develop revamp campaign detail especially fund detail.
- Technical Skills: Typescript, Javascript, ReactJs, NextJS, Git, TailwindCss

Stafbook Jakarta, Indonesia

Frontend Developer (Freelance)

Apr 2022 - Aug 2022

· Slice design to code.

- Develop landing page stafbook.
- Develop main app stafbook.
- Technical Skills: Typescript, NextJS, Git, Tailwind CSS, Zuustand

Blocknom (YC W22) Jakarta, Indonesia

Frontend Developer (Freelance)

Feb 2022 - Apr 2022

- · Slice design to code.
- · Revamp landing page.
- Develop main app blocknom.
- Technical Skills: Typescript, NextJS, Git, Tailwind CSS, Redux

PUTI - Telkom University Bandung, Indonesia

Frontend Developer Mar 2021 - Apr 2022

- · Working on an internal project for the international office app for managing student permits its called permit service.
- Contribute to work on an application project to manage the certification of Telkom University employees and students called DigiTrain.
- · Develop dashboard portal data for academic Telkom university.
- Technical Skills: Typescript, Javascript, ReactJs, AngularJS, Git, SCSS, Bootstrap.

Vallet Bandung, Indonesia

Jan 2020 - Apr 2020

- · Manage assets images at vallet app.
- Take image assets for publish on vallet app.
- Make assets like poster, banner etc.
- Technical Skills: Photoshop. Vallet app (design tools), Photography.

Inovasi Semesta Ilmu (INOSI)

Bandung, Indonesia

Jan 2018 - Feb 2018

Develop augmented reality virtual tour Bandung.

• Technical Skills: C#, Unity 3D.

Skills

Internship

Internship

Programming Javascript, Typescript, Nodejs, Vanila CSS, Tailwind Css, NextJs

Miscellaneous Linux, Git, Markdown, Vim.

Soft Skills Time Management, Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation.

DECEMBER 19, 2022

2022 **Kitabisa Hackaton (Social Safety Nets Theme)**, Favourite champion

Jakarta

Languages _____

English Professional proficiency

Indonesia Native

DECEMBER 19, 2022 2